Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
- Flight Engineers' International Association, Publication (Box 537, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1983; Publication (Box 537, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws, 1989; Publication (Box 537, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Constitution and by-laws, 1989; Publication (Box 537, Folder 4)
- Flight Engineers' International Association, Publication (Box 537, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and the Flight Engineers in the service of Pan American World Airways, Inc. as represented by the Flight Engineers' International Association, PAA Chapter, AFL/CIO: August 6, 1970, Publication (Box 537, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and its Flight Engineers as represented by Flight Engineers' International Association: January 1, 1988, Publication (Box 537, Folder 5)
- UFCW (United Food and Commercial Workers International Union), Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Tempo, 1985; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 1985.
  - Item 2: Tempo, 1985; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 1985.
  - Item 3: On May 22, 1981, Local 919 President, Arnaldo F. Expinosa, sent the following self explanatory letter to all the members of the UFCW Exec. Bd., Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Analyzing ergonomic programs: making sure they are the real thing, 1989; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Analyzing ergonomic programs: making sure they are the real thing, 1989; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Labor's centennial celbrates 100 years of progress, 1981; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Labor's centennial celbrates 100 years of progress, 1981; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The labor unions, Dun & Bradstreet, and dialog the attempt to restrict access, 1988; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Don't buy Perdue chickens: a fact book, 1981; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Don't buy Perdue chickens: a fact book, 1981; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Warning, your workplace may be hazardous to your safety and your health: UFCW safety and health manual, 1983; Publication (Box 538, Folder 1)
- UFCW (United Food and Commercial Workers International Union), Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Lie detector drama: victims and villains, 1980-1981 (Box 538, Folder 2)
    Notes: Flyer.
  - Item 2: Union goals: what can we offer?, 1980-1981 (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: How much is your life worth?, 1980-1981 (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: A union preparing today for the needs of tomorrow, 1980-1981 (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: UFCW: the Professional's choice, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: UFCW: a union on the move, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Sexual harassment: its not flattering, its not your fault, its against the law and the UFCW can help, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The church speaks on labor unions, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: UFCW: the Professional's choice, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: UFCW: a union on the move, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Sexual harassment: its not flattering, its not your fault, its against the law and the UFCW can help, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: The church speaks on labor unions, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: To All our friends around the world, UFCW and Local 919 settle dispute, 1981; Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Don't buy Perdue chickens because this company treats its workers, the public, and consumers like they aren't human, 1981; Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Don't buy Perdue chickens because this company treats its workers, the public, and consumers like they aren't human, 1981; Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: To All our friends around the world, Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: UFCW economic dislocation manual, 198; Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Job stress: a discussion guide and slide show, 1986; Publication (Box 538, Folder 2)
- UFCW (United Food and Commercial Workers International Union), Publication (Box 538, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution - July 1993; July 1988, 1988-1993 (Box 538, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: In the Supreme Court of the United States, October term, 1979: Retail Store Employees Union, Local No. 919; Arnaldo F. Espinosa, et al., Petitioners, v. United Food and Commercial Workers International Union; William H. Wynn, et al., Respondents: Petition, 1980; Publication (Box 538, Folder 3)
- UFCW (United Food and Commercial Workers International Union), Publication (Box 538, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Stop & Shop Supermarket Company and Local Union 328, chartered by the United Food and Commercial Workers Union International Union, AFL-CIO-CLC: effective date: June 2, 1991, expiration date: May 28, 1994, 1991-1994 (Box 538, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining agreement by and between Woodward & Lothrop Incorporated (Company) and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 400 (Union), 1979; Publication (Box 538, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Wilson Foods Corporation and United Food & Commercial Workers Union International Union, AFL-CIO & CLC: June 27, 1983 to September 1, 1985, 1983-1985 (Box 538, Folder 4)
- American Flint Glass Workers Union, Publication (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: National Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: National Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: National Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 539, Folder 1)
- American Flint Glass Workers Union, Publication (Box 539, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: History and archives of the American Flint Glass Workers Union, 1978; Publication (Box 539, Folder 2)
    Author: George M. Parker
  - Item 2: History and archives of the American Flint Glass Workers Union, 1978; Publication (Box 539, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: More than a century of dedication to workers of the glass industry: brief history of the American Flint Glass Workers Union AFL-CIO 1878-1978, Publication (Box 539, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: More than a century of dedication to workers of the glass industry: brief history of the American Flint Glass Workers Union AFL-CIO 1878-1978, Publication (Box 539, Folder 2)
- Indiana State Employees Association, Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: ISEA Legislative News, 1984; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.3 (1984)
  - Item 2: ISEA Newbrief, 1984; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: Special Advance Edition (1984)
  - Item 3: Constitution and bylaws, 1980; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Constitution and bylaws, 1980; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Hotline Age, 1981; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 15, 1981.
  - Item 6: Hotline Age, 1982; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: March 1982.
  - Item 7: Hotline Age, 1983; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: December 26, 1983.
  - Item 8: Hotline Age, 1984; Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: March 1984.
  - Item 9: CoverAge - vol. 29, no. 1 (1980), Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1980)
  - Item 10: CoverAge - vol. 29, no. 1 (1980), Publication (Box 539, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1980). Copy 2.
- AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), Publication (Box 539, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement between U.S. Immigration and Naturalization Service and National Immigration and Naturalization Service Council, Publication (Box 539, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Immigration and Naturalization Service and American Federation of Government Employees, National Immigration and Naturalization Services Council, 1990; Publication (Box 539, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Collective agreement between Local 12 American Federation of Government Employees AFL-CIO and United States Department of Labor, 1980; Publication (Box 539, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: General agreement U.S.Civil Service Commission Central Office and American Federation of Government Employees, AFL/CIO, Local 32, 1974; Publication (Box 539, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the U.S. Department of Labor and the National Council of Field Labor Locals, American Federation of Government Employees, AFL-CIO: August 17, 1978 agreement including clarifications and amendments through September 1, 1985, 1978-1985 (Box 539, Folder 4)
- AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Another benefit for you, Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Life insurance protection, Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Welcome, rest confidently. You have many friends, Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: AFGE health benefit plan, Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Labor-management agreement between the National Archives and Records Administration and the American Federation of Government Employees: effective April 2, 1987, Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Master agreement between the Veterans Administration and the American Federation of Government Employees: August 1982, Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Master agreement between the Veterans Administration and the American Federation of Government Employees: August 1982, Publication (Box 539, Folder 5)
- AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), Publication (Box 539, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of agreement Saint Lawrence Seaway Development Corporation and Local No. 1968, American Federation of Government Employees: approved September 16, 1987, Publication (Box 539, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Collective agreement between Local 12 American Federation of Government Employees AFL-CIO and United States Department of Labor, 1980; Publication (Box 539, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the United States Department of Labor and the National Council of Field Labor Locals, American Federation of Government Employees, AFL-CIO: Effective October 1, 1991, Publication (Box 539, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Local 12, AFGE, AFL-CIO and the U. S. Department of Labor: Effective March 15, 1992, Publication (Box 539, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Local 12, AFGE, AFL-CIO and the U. S. Department of Labor: Effective March 15, 1992, Publication (Box 539, Folder 6)
- AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Organized labor in the Federal sector and the growth of relations: a capsule history, Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Organized labor in the Federal sector and the growth of AFGE: a capsule history, Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Organized labor in the Federal sector and the growth of AFGE: a capsule history, Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
    Notes: Photocopy
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Stewards manual, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: AFGE-Federal union: the story of the American Federation of Government Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 540, Folder 1)
    Author: Jack Nevin; Lorna Nevin
    Notes: 3 copy
- AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: AFGE News - Statement by John N. Sturdivant, Natl. Pres., American Federation of Government Employees, 1993; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Joseph D. Gleason, Executive Vice President, American Federation of Governement Employees, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
    Notes: News release.
  - Item 3: Joseph D. Gleason, Executive Vice President, American Federation of Governement Employees, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
    Notes: News release. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Nicholas J. Nolan, National Secretary-Treasurer, American Federation of Government Employees, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Kenneth T. Blaylock, Natl. President, American Federation of Government Employees, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Political Action Committee - "Continuing his attack on federal workers and retirees, President Bush again this year tried to push through budget proposals that would have unfairly targeted your pay and benefits in the name of deficit reduction", 1992; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Political Action Committee - "Continuing his attack on federal workers and retirees, President Bush again this year tried to push through budget proposals that would have unfairly targeted your pay and benefits in the name of deficit reduction", 1992; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: AFGE Bulletin, 1992; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.8:no.18/19 (1992)
  - Item 9: AFGE News - AFGE endorses Bill Clinton for President, 1992; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: 1991 Labor history calendar, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Special Edition - The Government Standard, 1979; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Why you should join the AFGE, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Report of the National Office, American Federation of Government Employees to the 25th Biennial Convention, Sept. 20-24, 1976, Las Vegas, Nevada, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Collective bargaining: an AFGE guide to negotiations: a guide to collective bargaining in the federal sector under the Federal Service-Labor-Management Relations Statute, 1984; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Collective bargaining: an AFGE guide to negotiations: a guide to collective bargaining in the federal sector under the Federal Service-Labor-Management Relations Statute, 1984; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Collective bargaining: American Federation of Government Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Total quality partnership: a vision for the future, 1993; Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Union duesan investment!, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Women's place is in the AFGE, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: What is the AFGE?, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Equality, Equal Women, American Federation, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Professionals.American Federation, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: The questions we most-often hear on Civil Service Reform?, Publication (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Executive order 11491: as amended by Executive order 11616, 11636 and 11838 Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Service, American Federation of Government Employees (AFL- CIO), 1969-1975 (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Executive order 11491: as amended by Executive order 11616, 11636 and 11838 Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Service, American Federation of Government Employees (AFL- CIO), 1969-1975 (Box 540, Folder 2)
- AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), Publication (Box 540, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: State Economic data trends: a survey covering the period - 1977-1982 (Box 540, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: A Study of state government employee benefits, 1982; Publication (Box 540, Folder 3)
- National Association of Municipal Employees, Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Hotline Age - National Legislative Update, 1981; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
    Notes: October 30, 1981.
  - Item 2: The largest independent government employees union, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Police Chronicle, 1986; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.14:no.4 (1986:Nov./Dec.)
  - Item 4: The Police Chronicle, 1986; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.14:no.4 (1986:Nov./Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: FedNews, 1986; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.3 (1986:July/Aug.)
  - Item 6: FedNews, 1986; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.3 (1986:July/Aug.). Copy 2.
  - Item 7: NAGE Reporter, 1986; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1986:Sep./Oct.)
  - Item 8: NAGE Reporter, 1986; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1986:Sep./Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: Constitution and by-laws, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Constitution and by-laws, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Constitution and by-laws, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Constitution and by-laws, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Constitution and by-laws, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Constitution and by-laws, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Constitution and by-laws, 1980; Publication (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Negotiated agreement between Watervliet Arsenal and National Association of Goverment(sic) Employees, Local R2-98: 14 September 1977 as supplemented 6 April 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 540, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 540, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Complete agreement between Standard Milling Company and American Federation of Grain Millers (photo copy), 1981; Publication (Box 540, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws - 1993, 1991, 1991-1993 (Box 540, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: General Mills: Supplemental agreement between General Mills, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 540, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: General Mills: Supplemental agreement between General Mills, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 540, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Master agreement between General Mills, Inc. and American Federation of Grain Millers (AFL-CIO): relating to the Company's Plant at, effective from: April 1, 1978 to April 1, 1981, 1978-1981 (Box 540, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Do you have a complaint or a grievance?, Publication (Box 540, Folder 5)
- Granite Cutters' International Association of America, Publication (Box 540, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1971; Publication (Box 540, Folder 6)
- National Football League. Players Association, Publication (Box 540, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Q. Why a percentage of gross? A. Because we are the game: a report to members of the National Football League Players Association, September 1981., Publication (Box 540, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining agreement between National Football League Players Association and National Football League Management Council: Dated: March 1, 1977, Publication (Box 540, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining agreement NFL Management Council, 1977; Publication (Box 540, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining agreement between National Football League Players Association and National Football League Management Council, 1982, Publication (Box 540, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: news clipping - Labor Mediator Horvitz to be named to U.S. Post, Publication (Box 540, Folder 7)
- National Footbal League. Players Association, Publication (Box 541, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 541, Folder 1)
- United Furniture Workers of America, Publication (Box 541, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1984; Publication (Box 541, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Kittinger Company, Division of General Interiors Corporation and Local Union No. 39, United Furniture Workers of America, AFL-CIO: 1974-1976 (Box 541, Folder 2)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 541, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1987; Publication (Box 541, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Agreement Snow Suit, Skiwear, Leggings and Infants' Novelty Wear Workers' Union, Local 105, I.L.G.W.U. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, I.L.G.W.U. with Infants' and Children's Coat, 1970-1973 (Box 541, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Children's Dress, Infants' Wear, Housedress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, Local 91, I.L.G.W.U., Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10, I.L.G.W.U. and Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers, Inc.: Collective agreement: 1970-19, 1970-1973 (Box 541, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and Corset and Brassiere Workers of New York, Local 32 and Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, 1974; Publication (Box 541, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear and Allied Workers' Union and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union with New York Coat and Suit Association, Inc. and Infants', Children's & Girl's Sportswear and Coat Association, Inc.: Collective agreement, 19, 1985-1988 (Box 541, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear and Allied Workers' Union and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union with New York Coat and Suit Association, Inc. and Infants', Children's & Girl's Sportswear and Coat Association, Inc.: Collective agreement, 19, 1982-1985 (Box 541, Folder 3)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: AIM Report, 1992; Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Associate ILGWU Member, for a better tomorrow, 1992; Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Welcome to New York birthplace of the ILGWU, Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: A manual for trade union speakers: a brief text book on public speaking, 1936; Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
    Author: August Claessens
  - Item 7: Where do we go from here?: an address to the Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt Centennial Conference of the Americans for Democratic Action, March 6, 1982, Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
    Author: Sol C. Chaikin
  - Item 8: Why education is a must in the ILGWU, Publication (Box 541, Folder 4)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 541, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program, Publication (Box 541, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Your union: Shop Officer's workbook, Publication (Box 541, Folder 5)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 541, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A manual for trade union speakers: a brief text book on public speaking, 1936; Publication (Box 541, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Employer contributed benefit funds International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1983; Publication (Box 541, Folder 6)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: ILGWU cares about plan members, 1994; Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Dust dust dust, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
    Notes: Article
  - Item 3: Fire prevention & protection checklist, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Formaldehyde, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Noise, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Asbestos, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Shop inspection checklist, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Carpal tunnel syndrome, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Job health & safety, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Your OSHA rights, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Information access: health and safety documents you have a right to under the law, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Solvents, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Hazard communication, your right to know, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Heat, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Isolating job stresses, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Make your chair & table work for you, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Noise, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Back belts, Publication (Box 541, Folder 7)